A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19 FA291
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
1863-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Harkness, Edward Stephen
Harkness, Charles W.
Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman
Harkness, Anna M. Richardson
Commonwealth Fund
FA291
15.67 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement note
This series is arranged in two subseries:
Subseries 1: Documents
Subseries 2: Bound Volumes and Ephemera
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Scope and Contents note
The Harkness Family Papers are the private records of Edward S. and Mary S. Harkness. These documents are concerned with their donations to universities, schools, institutions and individuals. There is a great quantity of information on donations to schools and universities like Phillips Exeter Academy, Columbia, Harvard, Yale and others. There is a book on the residential halls of Yale University in the Harkness Family Volumes. The Harkness Family provided funds for organizations like the Pilgrim Trust in which further information can be found in the Harkness Family Volumes. There are other institutions which the Harkness family contributed to like Presbyterian Hospital, New York Public Library and the Metropolitan Museum of Art. Gifts and donations for servants, friends and family are documented. Members of the family include the Russels, the Stillmans and the Taylors. There are records of the Harkness family. These are mostly concerned with Edward S. Harkness' Estate and Trust after his death. The Harkness Family Volumes contains condolences offered at his death. The Harkness Family papers were examined by Malcolm P. Aldrich, Trustee of the Edward S. Harkness Estate. These documents consist mostly of correspondence, financial data, legal documents and reports.
The Harkness Family Volumes are the business, personnel and condolence documents of Anna M. (AMH), Charles W., Edward S. (ESH), Mary S. (MSH) and Stephen E. Harkness. The business and personnel records relate to the Family. The condolence volumes are concerned with the death of Edward S. Harkness. Information concerning his death can be found in the Harkness Family Papers too. There are two volumes on institutions in which Edward S. Harkness was involved, the Pilgrim Trust and Yale University. Further information on these institutions can be found in the Harkness Family Papers. This collection contains correspondence, legal documents and volumes.
Mental health; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Medicine, Rural; Hygiene; Law; Child welfare; Education, Rural; Medical education; Medical research; Legal issues; Legal research; Public welfare; Public health; War relief; United States; Child mental health; Child psychology; New York (State); New York (N.Y.)
- Documents, 1874-1982; 1
  - Antique Collecting, 1915-1930 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta University, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bayonne Housing Corporation, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beasley, Ada, 1938-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Billings House, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bird, Virgo E. and Anita, 1923-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Blockage (AMH Estate Taxes), July 29, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1922-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Columbia University (Barnard College), 1918-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Columbia University (Distribution ESH Trust), 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Columbia University (New Library Building), 1930-1935 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Columbia University (Thank You to ESH), May 4, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Distribution ESH Trust), 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Securities from AMH), 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Community Service Society, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut College (Contributions for Harkness Chapel), 1923-1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Davidson, Florence T., 1917-1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ellis, Alfred D. G., 1919-1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Farmers Federation Educational and Development Fund, July 23-31, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Greenwood Cemetery (MSH Plot/Family Grave Sites), [1938] (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hampton Institute, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Harkness, Charles W. (Ledgers of Donation Accounts), 1904-1919 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Commonwealth Fund Donations), 1922-1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Accounts), 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Certificate Deed), October 9, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Commissions), 1940-1945 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Decree), August 27, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Distribution), 1944-1951 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted - Confidential material.
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Distribution), 1944-1951 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Distribution), 1944-1951 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Distribution), 1944-1951 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Distribution), 1944-1951 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Federal Tax Data), 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Federal Tax Data), January 29, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Intermediate Accounts), 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Inventories), 1940-1950 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Inventories), 1940-1950 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Legacies), 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Letters of Trusteeship), March 15, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Receipts and Releases), October 4-17, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Reductions and Increases), 1942-1945 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Report), 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Report), 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Schedule C), 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Supplemental Affidavit), August 15, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Trust), 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Trust), 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Trust), 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Estate Will), 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Receipt and Release), 1926-1941 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Releases), 1943-1951 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust), 1949-1951 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Distribution), 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Eolia Estate), 1909-1951 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Indemnity), June 14, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Miscellaneous), 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Secondary Distributions), 1940-1942 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Surrogate's Court Account), September 30, 1940; 1945-1950 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Surrogate's Court Account), September 30, 1940; 1945-1950 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Harkness, Edward S. (Trust Will of ESH), 1940-1950 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Mary S. (Address Book - 654 Madison Avenue Office), 1930-1939 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Mary S. (Contributions), 1925-1950 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Mary S. (Contributions), 1925-1950 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Mary S. (Employee Records), 1930-1950 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Mary S. (Personnel Records - 654 Madison Avenue Office)), 1940-1950 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Estate Final Account), September 28, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Estate Petition for Voluntary Accounting), October 4, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Estate Supplemental Affidavit), September-December, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Historical Information), 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Personnel List), June-July, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Harkness, Mary S. (Regular Remittances), 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Harvard University - College Subdivision (Donations), 1923-1950 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Harvard University - College Subdivision (Donations), 1923-1950 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Harvard University - College Subdivision (Donations), 1923-1950 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Harvard University - College Subdivision (Donations), 1923-1950 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Harvard University - College Subdivision (Donations and Housing), 1928-1929 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Harvard University - College Subdivision (Donations and Housing), 1932-1949 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Harvard University - Distribution of ESH Estate, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hawkins, Louise R., 1926-1949 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Husted Family, 1935-1950 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Lawrenceville (New Jersey) School, 1929-1949 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Loans, 1909-1944 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Lythgoe Trust (ESH for Albert M. Lythgoe), 1929-1932 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Marine Historical Association (Thomas Greenman Property, Mystic Seaport), 1941-1970 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Miller, John Richardson (Trust Fund), 1913-1936 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Gifts), 1950-1964 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Release of Harkness Portraits to MSH), February 16, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Morrow, Lowell Howard, 1925-1950 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Museum of the City of New York (Photo of ESH at King George VI Coronation), November 12-22, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Newell, Elizabeth K. (Mrs. George M. Newell), 1938-1950 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - New York Public Library - Donations, 1948-1963 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - New York Public Library - ESH Will (Donations), 1941-1982 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Oberlin College - Donations for Harkness Hall, 1923-1949 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Oil Companies (Anti-Trust Case), January-July, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Phillips Academy (Andover, Massachusetts) - Donations for Buildings, 1919-1948 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Phillips Academy (Andover, Massachusetts) - Donations for Buildings, 1919-1948 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Phillips Academy (Andover, Massachusetts) - Donations for Buildings, 1919-1948 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy (Exeter, New Hampshire) - Donations, 1919, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy (Exeter, New Hampshire) - Donations, 1919, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy (Exeter, New Hampshire) - Donations, 1931-1941 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy (Exeter, New Hampshire) - Donations for New Buildings, 1932-1949 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy (Exeter, New Hampshire) - Donations for New Buildings, 1932-1949 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy (Exeter, New Hampshire) - Donations for New Buildings, 1932-1949 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Pilgrim Trust - Establishment and Administration, 1930-1949 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Pilgrim Trust - Formation and Deed, 1930-1952 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Pilgrim Trust - Formation and Deed, 1930-1952 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Pledges, April-October, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Presbyterian Hospital - Distribution Under Trust, June-September, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Presbyterian Hospital - Endowment of Two Beds, 1898-1927 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Presbyterian Hospital - Pledges for ESH Memorial Hall and Pavilion, 1911-1922; 1925-1948 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Presbyterian Hospital - Pledges for ESH Memorial Hall and Pavilion, 1911-1922; 1925-1948 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Presbyterian Hospital II - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1910-1937 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Presbyterian Hospital II - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1910-1937 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Presbyterian Hospital II - Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1910-1937 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Russell Family, 1921-1946 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Sage, Gray, Todd and Sims (Counsellors at Law), 1874-1955 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - St. Andrews University (Articles on ESH), March-May, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - St. Paul's School - Donations, 1937-1953 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - St. Paul's School - Gifts and Buildings, 1931-1964 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - St. Paul's School - Gifts and Buildings, 1931-1964 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Salisbury, Frank O. (ESH Portrait), 1932-1939 (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - Special Gifts for Medical Activities, 1937-1953 (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - Stillman, Florence, 1936-1942 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Stillman, Lisa, 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 134)
  - Stillman, Michael, 1944-1945 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Stillman, Mr. and Mrs. Michael, 1944-1948 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Stillman, Thomas E., 1912-1925 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - Stock Costs (American Telephone and Telegraph Company; Standard Oil), 1917-1949 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Taylor, Jessie Stillman, 1943-1946 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Taylor, Jessie Stillman, 1943-1946 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - Thomas, John Anderson, November 5-10, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - Various Organizations (Historical Data), 1896-1950 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - Weekend (Appraisal of Estate), 1940-1944 (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - Weekend (Sale of), 1940-1944 (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Woodlawn Cemetery, 1921-1974 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Woodlawn Cemetery, 1921-1974 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Yale University - Art Gallery Extension, 1924-1945 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Yale University - Bursary and Masters Funds, 1929-1942 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - Yale University - College Plan, 1926-1955 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Yale University - Contributions, 1936-1940 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Yale University - Distributions under Trust, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - Yale University - Drama School, 1924-1947 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - Yale University - Endowment Drive, 1920-1932 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Yale University - Foreign Missionary Society/Hsiangya Hospital (Yale in China), 1933-1948 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Commonwealth Fund Grant Series, Hunan-Yale College of Medicine, Changsha, China, Box 147, Folders 1347-1349.
  - Yale University - Library, 1926-1965 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Yale University - Medical School, 1914-1951 (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - Yale University - Memorial Quadrangle (Branford and Saybrook Colleges), 1916-1950 (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - Yale University - President's Fund for Educational Supervision, 1929-1942 (Box 15, Folder 158)
  - Yale University - President's Fund for Educational Supervision, 1929-1942 (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - Yale University - Record of Contributions, January 3, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Pledges), 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Pledges), 1927-1929 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Reports on the New Quadrangle System), 1929-1940 (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Reports on the New Quadrangle System), 1929-1940 (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Reports on the New Quadrangle System), 1929-1940 (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Reports on the New Residential Halls), 1929-1952 (Box 16, Folder 166)
  - Yale University - Residence Halls (Reports on the New Residential Halls), 1929-1952 (Box 16, Folder 167)
  - Yale University - Residential Units (Berkeley College), 1929-1941 (Box 16, Folder 168)
  - Yale University - Residential Units (Berkeley College), 1929-1941 (Box 16, Folder 169)
  - Yale University - Residential Units (Timothy Dwight College), 1934-1941 (Box 16, Folder 170)
  - Yale University - Residential Units (Jonathan Edwards College, Pierson College and Trumball College), 1933-1941 (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - Yale University - Tapestries, 1925-1947 (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - Yale University - Theatre, 1924-1937 (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - Yale University - Treasurer Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 16, Folder 174)
- Bound Volumes and Ephemera, 1863-1973; 2
  - American College of Physicians - Edward R. Loveland Memorial Award to Trustees of the Common Wealth Fund, 1973 April 9 (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Appeals
    - I, 1918-1926 (Box 17, Folder 176)
    - II, 1927-1939 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - III, 1940-1950 (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Mary S.
    - Index to Donations, 1930-1940 (Box 18, Folder 179)
    - List of Regular Contributions to Individuals, Jan 4, 1918 - June 16, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 180)
  - Harkness, Anna M., Charles W., and Edward S. - Donation Records, February 28, 1896 - May 1909 (Box 19, Folder 181)
  - Harkness, Anna M. and Charles W. - Ledger of Accounts, August 28, 1863 - October 11, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 182)
  - Harkness, Stephen E. and Anna M. - Ledger of Deeds, October 4, 1869 - June 4, 1909 (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - Harkness, Edward S. - Ledger of Real Estate Plots, January 7, 1899 - August 8, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Harkness, Anna M. - Journal: Real Estate Transactions in Ohio, January 3, 1899 - December 31, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Harkness Reports, 1931-1949 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Harkness, Edward S.
    - Trust Register of Cash Distributions, January 26, 1942 - August 28, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 187)
    - Trust Register of Cash Distributions, January 26, 1942 - August 28, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 188)
  - Harkness, Edward S. and Anna M.
    - Wage Book and Expenses, March 1, 1917 - July 15, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - Wage Book, August 3, 1919 - September 1, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 190)
  - Ledger Pages - Missellaneous, 1896-1898, 1937-1949 (Box 23, Folder 191)
  - Harkness Scrapbooks
    - No. I, 1925-1936 (Box 31, Folder 201)
    - Harkness Scrapbooks - No. 1, 1932; 2015:FA291:001 (Box 2015:FA291:001)
    - No. II, 1940-1949 (Box 31, Folder 202)
    - Clippings, 1925-1950 (Box 31, Folder 203)
  - Harkness, Edward S. - Condolences Books
    - Flowers, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - Letters Vol. I, January 29, 1940 - February 14, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 193)
    - Letters Vol. II, January 29, 1940 - February 14, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 194)
    - Letters Vol. III, January 29, 1940 - February 14, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 195)
    - Letters Vol. IV, Januart 29, 1940 - February 14, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 196)
    - Letters Vol. V, January 30, 1940 - February 14, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 197)
    - Newspaper Articles, January 30, 1940 - February 7, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 198)
    - Resolutions, February 12, 1940 - April 24, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 199)
    - Telegrams, January 29, 1940 - February 2, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 200)
  - Memorials
    - Boy Scout Foundation of Greater New York, 1940 February 21 (Box 32, Folder 204)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1940 January 29 (Box 32, Folder 205)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1940 April 25 (Box 32, Folder 206)
    - The Presbyterian Hospital in the City of New York, 1926 June 8, 1940 February 13 (Box 32, Folder 207)
    - Southern Pacific Company, 1940 February 1 (Box 32, Folder 208)
    - University of St. Andrews, 1940 February 4 (Box 32, Folder 209)
    - Wells College, 1941 June 9 (Box 32, Folder 210)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Mary Stillman Harkness, 1950 October 19 (Box 32, Folder 211)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Barbara Story Quin, 1945 October 11 (Box 32, Folder 212)
  - Philadelphia Child Guidance Clinic
    - Statistical Manual, 1924-1927 (Box 33, Folder 213)
    - 1927-1937 (Box 33, Folder 214)
  - Pilgrim Trust
    - First Annual Report, 1931-1933 (Box 34, Folder 215)
    - Scrapbook, 1930-1933 (Box 34, Folder 216)
  - Yale Residential Colleges - Photograph and Essay Book, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 217)